foreign
[Music]
is here there is a lovely chill in the
air and everything is so beautiful
and today I thought I would take you
along to a Saturday at my Bookshop where
I work on the weekend
foreign
[Music]
settled into my job and usually begin
the day with my co-worker and dear
friend tidying up and making sure
everything is ready for opening
I then may work on putting the back
stock out on the shelves alphabetizing
and making sure that everything is
updated
[Music]
I may spend time cleaning dust away and
of course chatting with customers about
books I actually don't have time to read
while working here however sometimes
when no one is in the shop and it's a
quiet winter evening and all my duties
are done for the day I have been known
to read a page or two but that's the
secret
thank you
[Music]
I am not very good at alphabetizing and
doing certain things but I am learning
and getting better with time
usually by the end of the day my feet
are a bit sore but I always find it
enjoyable to spend time in the company
of books and my lovely co-worker
but by the evening I'm on my way home
again often with a new book or two as we
do have access to a lot of free books
which is a wonderful benefit of the job
[Music]
foreign
with customizing some books that I
wanted to give as Christmas gifts
[Music]
foreign
so I spent the evening customizing these
books that I want to hopefully give as
Christmas gifts so there is a fun idea
for you if you like to gift books but
you would like to add something a little
more personal of course I looked at
photos online of entire murals that are
put on these books sometimes that are
extremely detailed and just beautiful
and I knew I wouldn't have time to do
something that detailed I also suspect
that getting the proper type of paints
to do highly detailed work like that
could be quite expensive so I thought
that perhaps you'd be inspired by this
more simple version of it that's quite
inexpensive and it's just using gel pens
or gel markers and with a delicate touch
you can get quite adorable results even
though they might not be quite as
sophisticated one thing I love is that
if you open the book you can write a
little message in the pages that then
and it disappears once you close the
book and so the reader will only get
that very personal message from you once
they open the book I definitely
recommend picking up a few books that
are used or very inexpensive that you
can practice on before you try to
customize one of your favorite books
with all that being said I hope you
enjoyed this little video I did want to
share a little bit of an update of what
it's like to work at my bookstore I have
really settled in over the last several
months and the first time I made a very
similar video I had only just started at
the bookstore and so I have a lot more
responsibilities now and other things
that I have learned so I just wanted to
kind of share an update on that but yes
I was looking at my old video I'll link
it down below about working at a
bookstore when I first started working
there and I remember saying that I got
um paid 14 an hour and the average
paperback book with my employee discount
is about fourteen dollars so I was
pretty much just recycling my paycheck
back into the store that is still very
true
I am quite at peace with being a book
collector because I do not prioritize
kind of brand new books which would be
quite expensive I love to buy used books
Advanced readers copies that I get as a
Bookseller also just you know any sort
of thrifted or you know kind of older
book
if you do keep track of my videos you'll
know that I was Ill last month and I did
start reading uh Shady Hollow so if you
do like cozy Mysteries this is a murder
mystery so you know
do with that what you will but reading
the rest of the series
um I really liked the second two books a
lot more than the first so I think that
they improved drastically with time and
the very last book which was Mirror Lake
was definitely my favorite if you don't
know why I was attracted to this book in
this series you're probably new to this
channel so put a Whimsical Woodland town
full of anthropomorphic animals and
outfits
with personalities
um in the middle of this kind of little
enchanted forest in a Perpetual Autumn
season
that is that is what I live for so of
course after finishing those books I
still wanted to read books with talking
animals and so I did ReDiscover an old
favorite that I read as a child and they
are the cottage Tales they do have
talking animals and of course they have
a heroine based off of the real life
Beatrix Potter and I thought they were
just lovely and probably exactly what I
want to read this Autumn thankfully each
one of them was about 75 cents to a
dollar because they're quite old and I
could only find them used so I'm looking
forward to reading these as well I
always feel kind of funny saying that I
enjoy these mystery books because many
of them do involve some kind of gruesome
moments in them reading a cozy Mysteries
kind of feels like a stage play you know
it's not realistic you know it's not
like true crime or a mystery that
actually puts you on the edge of your
seat you know it's more about the
Ambiance and the seasonal aspect usually
they're based on a season or have a
theme I've had some customers at the
bookstore refer to them as old lady
books and I love it because there are
many older women who have come in and
referred to them as their old lady book
because it's just embracing what you
like and knowing it might be perceived
as a guilty pleasure there is a very
eccentric and Whimsical old lady in my
heart that I will hopefully one day
become and I'm looking forward to
starting early with my obsession with
cozy Mysteries but yes I definitely have
been enjoying my time at the bookstore
if this is not the first job I had at a
bookstore I used to work at a bookstore
in my old University City and that one
was much larger than this one so that
was you know a different experience as
well I do really enjoy talking to
customers about books and book
recommendations particularly when
they're in the genres that I love to
read like adult fantasy it is of course
a customer service job so that aspect of
it you know can always be overwhelming
and exhausting at times so I know it is
definitely not for everyone and for some
people it really burns them out I wanted
to say really quick that I did restock
my little print of my mushroom bunny you
can only handle a small amount of orders
on my Etsy shop as I am doing all the
orders myself so I really do appreciate
your understanding that I do often have
to close my shop I was able to restock
my little bunny for at least a little
while and I wanted to let all of you
know who we're interested and I really
absolutely appreciate the support it
means the world let me know what you're
reading this October and I am sending
all of you my love please take care of
yourselves and I will see you very soon
foreign